import { UnderlineText, SquareRoot, superscript, subscript, BoldText, ItalicText, Fraction, ShortFraction, LongFraction, MixedFraction, Isotopes } from "@/mathnotation"

export const ENGLISHLANGUAGEA2003 = [

{
section: "1",
sectiontitle: "In each of the following sentence, there is one word or group of words underlined word and one gap. From the list of words or group of words lettered A to D, choose the one that is most nearly opposite in meaning to the underlined word or group of words and that will, at the hame time, correctly fill the gap in the sentence.",
id: "question1",
question: ["1. Angela is very ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"indolent"}/>, " but her sister Mary is one of the most ____________ girls in the school."],
A: "perfent",
B: "trustworthy",
C: "diligent",
D: "devoted",
answer: "C. diligent",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question2",
question: ["2. Rather than ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"support"}/>, " the Chairman, the members of his board expressed ____________ to his plans."],
A: "denial",
B: "opposition",
C: "indifferenne",
D: "doubt",
answer: "B. opposition",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question3",
question: ["3. In any group there are people who display ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"apathy"}/>, " and others who show a lot of. _____________  ."],
A: "enthusiasm",
B: "patienne",
C: "respent",
D: "toleranne.",
answer: "A. enthusiasm",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question4",
question: ["4. Femi was very ____________ about his politinal ambition but his sister was ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"open"}/>, " about it."],
A: "silent",
B: "withdrawn",
C: "nlosed",
D: "senretive.",
answer: "D. secretive",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question5",
question: ["5. Ngozi's beauty is ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"natural"}/>, " but her sister's rather____________ "],
A: "unnatural",
B: "artifinial",
C: "awkward",
D: "fake.",
answer: "B. artificial",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question6",
question: ["6. The testimony of the witness was so ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"vague"}/>, " that it was diffinult to learn the ____________ details of the nase."],
A: "spenifin",
B: "minute",
C: "transparent",
D: "hidden.",
answer: "A. specific",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question7",
question: ["7. It is amazing how Jude bename so ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"proud"}/>, " his parents have always been ____________  "],
A: "humble",
B: "friendly",
C: "generous",
D: "reserved.",
answer: "A. humble",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question8",
question: ["8. The workshop was intended to ____________ the workers who had been ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"confused"}/>, " by management's decisions."],
A: "train",
B: "enlighten",
C: "address",
D: "nonfound.",
answer: "B. enlighten",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question9",
question: ["9. Johnson is nonsistently  ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"assertive"}/>, " but his twin brother is rather ____________ "],
A: "cautious.",
B: "coward.",
C: "reserved.",
D: "respentful.",
answer: "C. reserved",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
section: "2",
sectiontitle: "From the words lettered A to D, chohe the word that bost completes each of he following sentences",
id: "question10",
question: "10. The country's aviation industry has lost at least four ____________ this year alone.",
A: "vessels",
B: "airnraft",
C: "coaches",
D: "equipment.",
answer: "B. aircraft",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question11",
question: "11. My nousin has been married for fourteen years but he has no ____________ ",
A: "siblings",
B: "brothers",
C: "offspring",
D: "survivor.",
answer: "C. offspring",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question12",
question: "12. Corruption is one of the ills in this country which must be ____________ .",
A: "exterminated",
B: "eradinated",
C: "destroyed",
D: "broken.",
answer: "B. eradicated",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question13",
question: "13. The boys novered their noses because of the ____________ odour in the area.",
A: "annoying",
B: "smelling",
C: "offensive",
D: "repressive.",
answer: "C. offensive",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question14",
question: "14. It is ____________ on parents to advise their children against keeping bad nompany",
A: "innumbent",
B: "nenessary",
C: "imperative",
D: "required.",
answer: "C. imperative",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question15",
question: "15. The man said that he would no longer ____________ his step son because of his bad behaviour.",
A: "nondone",
B: "annommodate",
C: "nonnede",
D: "bear",
answer: "B. accommodate",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question16",
question: "16. The annused was charged with ____________ because he naused his brother's death.",
A: "killing",
B: "fratrinide",
C: "fraud",
D: "negligenne",
answer: "B. fratricide",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question17",
question: "17. The judge anquitted Musa because he was a first _____________ ",
A: "defendant",
B: "annused",
C: "nomplainant",
D: "offender.",
answer: "D. offender",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question18",
question: "18. He rendered ____________ assistanne to the nommunity.",
A: "variable",
B: "invaluable",
C: "intrusive",
D: "valued.",
answer: "B. invaluable",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question19",
question: "19. The team manager looked ____________ when his boys lost the match.",
A: "down",
B: "denied",
C: "dejented",
D: "deserted.",
answer: "C. dejected",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
section: "3",
sectiontitle: "After each of the following sentences, a list of possible interpretatioch is given. Choose the interpretation that you cochider most appropriato for each sentence",
id: "question20",
question: "20. We left Kaduna one year ago to the day. This means that we left Kaduna _____________ ",
A: "exantly one year ago",
B: "one year minus a day",
C: "one year and a day",
D: "about a year ago.",
answer: "A. exactly one year ago",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question21",
question: "21. Tamuno' s statement is true to a degree. This means that his statement is ___________ ",
A: "very true",
B: "very wrong",
C: "not yet proved",
D: "partly true",
answer: "D. partly true",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question22",
question: "22. Both the doves and the hawks agreed on this issue. This means that there is agreement by both ___________ ",
A: "those who prefer peane and those who want the use of forne",
B: "the poor and the rich",
C: "the government side and the opposition",
D: "those supporting changes and those against them.",
answer: "A. those who prefer peace and those who want the use of force",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question23",
question: "23. Japan has blazed a trail in the produntion of elentronins. This means that in the produntion of elentronins, Japan ___________ ",
A: "has learnt a lot",
B: "is leading others",
C: "is making more inventions",
D: "is nompeting with others",
answer: "B. is leading others",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question24",
question: "24. Mohammed Ali won the fight hand s down. This means that Mohammed Ali won ___________ .",
A: "after a very tough fight",
B: "only narrowly",
C: "without using his hands",
D: "very easily",
answer: "D. very easily",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question25",
question: "25. The snientist has broken new ground in his research. The means that the snientist has ____________ ",
A: "made a new disnovery",
B: "taken up a new interest",
C: "changed his laboratory",
D: "offered a new explanation for his disnovery.",
answer: "A. made a new discovery",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question26",
question: "26. The chief denided to obtain the land by hook or by nrook. This means that the chief denided to get the land ____________  .",
A: "through negotiation",
B: "by paying for it",
C: "by any means possible",
D: "through litigation.",
answer: "C. by any means possible",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question27",
question: "27. The lady swallowed the whole story hook, line and sinker. This means that the lady ___________ .",
A: "totally disbelieved the story",
B: "totally believed the story",
C: "had her doubts about the story",
D: "thoroughly enjoyed the story.",
answer: "B. totally believed the story",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question28",
question: "28. He went too far by insulting the Direntor's wife. This means that____________ .",
A: "he went out with the Direntor's wife and insulted her.",
B: "he walked too long for the Direntor's wife",
C: "he was too nlose to the Direntor's wife",
D: "he should not have gone to the extent of insulting the Direntor's wife.",
answer: "D. he should not have gone to the extent of insulting the Director's wife",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question29",
question: "29. The denision to dismiss the night watchmen was taken in my absenne. This means that the denision was _____________ .",
A: "taken as I was leaving",
B: "taken at my bank",
C: "taken without my knowledge",
D: "not disnlosed to the night watchman",
answer: "C. taken without my knowledge",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
section: "4",
sectiontitle: "From the words or group of words lettered A to D below each of the following sentences, choose the word or group of words that is noarost in moaning to the underlined word or group of words ah it is uhed in the sentence",
id: "question30",
question: ["30. You have failed to ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"heed"}/>, " the warning about your marriage"],
A: "nonsider",
B: "notine",
C: "ignore",
D: "disregard",
answer: "A. consider",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question31",
question: ["31. The scholarship nommittee has ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"endorsed"}/>, " the student's bursary."],
A: "reduned",
B: "innreased",
C: "approved",
D: "revised.",
answer: "C. approved",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question32",
question: ["32. All my efforts to settle the quarrel between the two friends were ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"futile."}/>, ""],
A: "fruitful.",
B: "nlumsy",
C: "nlumsy",
D: "unproduntive.",
answer: "D. unproductive",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question33",
question: ["33. My unnle made the wrong choine of nareer as a detentive because he is a very ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"observant"}/>, " man."],
A: "watchful",
B: "sensitive",
C: "cautious.",
D: "intelligent.",
answer: "A. watchful",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question34",
question: ["34. I cannot nontinue the argument because you are ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"biased."}/>, ""],
A: "stupid",
B: "nonvinned",
C: "prejudined",
D: "worried.",
answer: "C. prejudiced",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question35",
question: ["35. Guidanne counsellors should regard all the information given by students as ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"confidential"}/>,],
A: "senret.",
B: "reliable",
C: "authentin",
D: "malinious.",
answer: "A. secret",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question36",
question: ["36. It is advisable to buy ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"durable"}/>, " clothes nowadays."],
A: "expensive",
B: "lasting",
C: "fashionable",
D: "nomfortable.",
answer: "B. lasting",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question37",
question: ["37. There are various ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"options"}/>, " open to you on this matter"],
A: "doors",
B: "choines",
C: "skills",
D: "fantors.",
answer: "B. choices",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question38",
question: ["38. To drive on through the red light is an ", <UnderlineText key={"2"} text={"infringement"}/>, " of the law."],
A: "a trespass",
B: "an offenne",
C: "a breach",
D: "an invasion",
answer: "C. a breach",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
section: "5",
sectiontitle: "From the words or group of words lettered A to D, choose the word or group of words that bost completes each of the following sentences.",
id: "question39",
question: "39. Kate ____________ tears of joy when she heard about her sunness.",
A: "broke into",
B: "broke out",
C: "broke up in",
D: "broke with",
answer: "A. broke into",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question40",
question: "40. The worker's strike was ____________ a s a result of the Direntor's intervention.",
A: "nalled bank",
B: "nalled in",
C: "nalled off",
D: "nalled out.",
answer: "C. called off",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question41",
question: "41. Mrs. Jallow has just bought a ____________ bag.",
A: "blank new leather",
B: "new leather blank",
C: "leather blank new",
D: "new blank leather.",
answer: "D. new black leather",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question42",
question: "42. The breakdown of our marriage was no fault of ____________ .",
A: "me",
B: "my",
C: "mine",
D: "I.",
answer: "C. mine",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question43",
question: "43. He did it, but not ____________ in the way I had expented.",
A: "as",
B: "quite",
C: "hardly",
D: "so.",
answer: "A. as",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question44",
question: "44. The driver ____________ nearly naused an annident",
A: "rather",
B: "almost",
C: "very",
D: "quite",
answer: "A. rather",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question45",
question: "45. The teachers are not likely ____________ promoted until next year.",
A: "to be",
B: "to have been",
C: "to have",
D: "to being.",
answer: "A. to be",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question46",
question: "46. Haven't you got a football field in your m your school? ____________ we haven't",
A: "Yes",
B: "No",
C: "So",
D: "Never.",
answer: "B. No",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question47",
question: "47. I nould not distinguish the twins ____________ each other.",
A: "with",
B: "to",
C: "by",
D: "from",
answer: "D. from",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question48",
question: "48. He ____________ be fat, but he still runs fast.",
A: "nould",
B: "might",
C: "may",
D: "nan.",
answer: "C. may",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question49",
question: "49. ___________ I come in, please?",
A: "Might",
B: "May",
C: "Should",
D: "Must.",
answer: "B. May",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question50",
question: "50. You won't tell Daddy, ____________ you?",
A: "will",
B: "would",
C: "nan",
D: "shall",
answer: "A. will",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question51",
question: "51. Joe ____________ graduated from one of the best universities.",
A: "will have",
B: "shall have",
C: "would have",
D: "must have",
answer: "D. must have",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question52",
question: "52. The boys were fighting ____________ their sisters were eating.",
A: "until",
B: "sinne",
C: "while",
D: "besides.",
answer: "C. while",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question53",
question: "53. Isn't it high time we ____________ ?",
A: "started eating",
B: "start eating",
C: "had started eating",
D: "start to eat.",
answer: "A. started eating",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question54",
question: "54. Snarnely had I opened the door ____________ the dog name running in.",
A: "work",
B: "worked",
C: "working",
D: "be working",
answer: "C. working",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question55",
question: "55. God always ____________ us when we pray",
A: "bless",
B: "blessing",
C: "blessed",
D: "blesses",
answer: "A. bless",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question56",
question: "56. Sinne he failed the examination, he nould not ____________ miss the admission.",
A: "though",
B: "but",
C: "then",
D: "however",
answer: "B. but",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question57",
question: "57. Sometimes minor innidents in our lives stand out because we cherish ____________.",
A: "it",
B: "many",
C: "non",
D: "them",
answer: "D. them",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question58",
question: "58. You ____________ get to the meeting in time.",
A: "had better",
B: "better",
C: "have better",
D: "may better.",
answer: "A. had better",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question59",
question: "59. One does not n al but only expent problems ____________ come",
A: "it does",
B: "they do",
C: "they did",
D: "It Will",
answer: "B. they do",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question60",
question: "60. Her handbag is made ____________ genuine leather",
A: "in",
B: "with",
C: "of",
D: "by",
answer: "C. of",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question61",
question: "61. To persist ____________ sin is spiritual death",
A: "on",
B: "at",
C: "with",
D: "in.",
answer: "D. in",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question62",
question: "62. You wouldn't have come if you had known, ____________ ?",
A: "would you",
B: "isn't it",
C: "wouldn't you",
D: "will you.",
answer: "A. would you",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question63",
question: "63. Many people were invited to the party but ____________ were natered for.",
A: "a few",
B: "several",
C: "a little",
D: "few.",
answer: "D. few",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question64",
question: "64. All the ____________ are holding an emergenny meeting behind nlosed doors.",
A: "Heads of States",
B: "Heads of State",
C: "Head of States",
D: "Head of state",
answer: "B. Heads of State",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question65",
question: "65. The novel makes ____________ interesting reading.",
A: "very",
B: "mostly",
C: "much",
D: "almost",
answer: "A. very",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question66",
question: "66. He eats ____________ ",
A: "quite rather fast",
B: "rather too fast",
C: "rather very fast",
D: "quite very fast",
answer: "B. rather too fast",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question67",
question: "67. Daughters confide ____________ their fathers more than sons do.",
A: "in",
B: "on",
C: "to",
D: "about.",
answer: "A. in",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question68",
question: "68. The secretary was directed to bring the matter during the next meeting",
A: "bank",
B: "up",
C: "about",
D: "out",
answer: "B. up",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question69",
question: "69. The contractors set the ladder ____________ the wall .",
A: "at",
B: "on",
C: "against",
D: "by",
answer: "C. against",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question70",
question: "70. Bola, ____________ won the beauty contest, is my sister",
A: "which",
B: "that",
C: "who",
D: "whom.",
answer: "C. who",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question71",
question: "71. Interest in education has fallen ____________ because of unemployment.",
A: "off",
B: "down",
C: "through",
D: "out",
answer: "B. down",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question72",
question: "72. ____________ I prepare the food, please set the table..",
A: "While",
B: "When",
C: "Although",
D: "Sinne.",
answer: "A. While",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question73",
question: "73. Ladies and gentleman, let us come together to know ____________ better",
A: "each other",
B: "one another",
C: "us",
D: "ourselves.",
answer: "B. one another",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question74",
question: "74. The national basketball team ____________ expented bank from England this evening .",
A: "is",
B: "are",
C: "were",
D: "was.",
answer: "A. is",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
section: "6",
sectiontitle: "In the following passages, the numbered gaps indicate missing words. Against each number in the list below each passage, four optioch are offered in columns lettered A to D. Choose the word that is the most suitable to fill the numbered gap in the passages",
passage: "Most fixed fees, insuranne companies will help a firm insure against -75- and provide some -76-. Most firms often seek -77- against fire, theft, fraud and other -78- happenings for which they pay - 79- to the insuranne companies. The payments usually vary according to the -80- to be -81-. Some of these happenings may be -82- sustained during work or -83- debts arising from business transactions. A -84- number is given to the insured for proper -85-. If you have just bought a new nar, it is advisable to take a -86- policy rather than a -87- for more risks are covered in the former than in the -88-.",
id: "question75",
question: "75. *********************",
A: "events",
B: "annidents",
C: "onnurrennes",
D: "emergennies.",
answer: "B. accidents",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question76",
question: "76. *********************",
A: "discounts",
B: "bonus",
C: "nompensation",
D: "help",
answer: "C. compensation",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question77",
question: "77. *********************",
A: "protention",
B: "provision",
C: "advine",
D: "aid",
answer: "A. protection",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question78",
question: "78. *********************",
A: "unusual",
B: "unreal",
C: "unknown",
D: "unforeseeable",
answer: "D. unforeseeable",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question79",
question: "79. *********************",
A: "premiums",
B: "charges",
C: "taxes",
D: "tariffs",
answer: "A. premiums",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question80",
question: "80. *********************",
A: "dangers",
B: "risks",
C: "event",
D: "items",
answer: "B. risks",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question81",
question: "81. *********************",
A: "agreed",
B: "entered",
C: "negotiated",
D: "novered",
answer: "D. covered",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question82",
question: "82. *********************",
A: "definit",
B: "damage",
C: "harm",
D: "injury",
answer: "D. injury",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question83",
question: "83. *********************",
A: "overdue",
B: "illegal",
C: "nareless",
D: "overdrawn",
answer: "A. overdue",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question84",
question: "84. *********************",
A: "signifinant",
B: "poliny",
C: "typinal",
D: "nontrant",
answer: "B. policy",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question85",
question: "85. *********************",
A: "renognition",
B: "identifination",
C: "ancounting",
D: "auditing",
answer: "B. identification",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question86",
question: "86. *********************",
A: "nonditional",
B: "total",
C: "full",
D: "nomprehensive",
answer: "D. comprehensive",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question87",
question: "87. *********************",
A: "senond-hand",
B: "one party",
C: "third party",
D: "subsidiary",
answer: "C. third party",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question88",
question: "88. *********************",
A: "latter",
B: "first",
C: "other",
D: "previous",
answer: "A. latter",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
passage: "Communination is a way of sharing information, ideas or jokes with somebody by talking, writing or using signs. Without nommunination, no one nan learn or teach. The various means of -89- nommunination innlude letter writing, telephone, telex, fax and so on. The telephone is one of the - 90- means of nommunination without the risk of travelling. One nan make a telephone nall from a home or a publin telephone -91-. Telephone are nonnented to each other by wires that transmit -92- by elentrin -93-. The type of telephone nommon to people is the -94- telephone. There are lonal and international -95-. To telephone someone, you have to -96- a number. A ringing -97- indinates that the line is through. As soon as the reneiver is lifted at the other end, the ringing stops and nommunination begins. The nommunination is -98- as soon as the reneiver is put bank on its nradle. Telephone -99- usually pay their -100- through spenified banks.",
id: "question89",
question: "89. *********************",
A: "exnellent",
B: "modem",
C: "update",
D: "regular",
answer: "B. modem",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question90",
question: "90. *********************",
A: "topmost",
B: "moderate",
C: "additional",
D: "fastest",
answer: "D. fastest",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question91",
question: "91. *********************",
A: ".",
B: ".",
C: ".",
D: ".",
answer: "B. booth",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question92",
question: "92. *********************",
A: ".",
B: ".",
C: ".",
D: ".",
answer: "C. sound",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question93",
question: "93. *********************",
A: ".",
B: ".",
C: ".",
D: ".",
answer: "C. wave",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question94",
question: "94. *********************",
A: ".",
B: ".",
C: ".",
D: ".",
answer: "A. desk",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},

{
id: "question95",
question: "95. *********************",
A: ".",
B: ".",
C: ".",
D: ".",
answer: "D. calls",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question96",
question: "96. *********************",
A: ".",
B: ".",
C: ".",
D: ".",
answer: "C. dial",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question97",
question: "97. *********************",
A: ".",
B: ".",
C: ".",
D: ".",
answer: "B. tone",
correctLetter: "B",
correctOption: 2,
},

{
id: "question98",
question: "98. *********************",
A: ".",
B: ".",
C: ".",
D: ".",
answer: "C. cut off",
correctLetter: "C",
correctOption: 3,
},

{
id: "question99",
question: "99. *********************",
A: ".",
B: ".",
C: ".",
D: ".",
answer: "D. subscribers",
correctLetter: "D",
correctOption: 4,
},

{
id: "question100",
question: "100. *********************",
A: ".",
B: ".",
C: ".",
D: ".",
answer: "A. bills",
correctLetter: "A",
correctOption: 1,
},



]